# MUHAMMAD ADHIM NIOKAGI

# Junior Web Developer | UI/UX Designer

Mojokerto, Jawa Timur | +6287755588990

https://linkedin.com/in/adhim-niokagi | https://nioka.netlify.app

I am a Junior Web Developer and a new student of Politeknik Elektronika Negeri Surabaya first semester, study program of Distance Education Informatics Engineering. Having good experience in the field of Administration and Information Technology, the skills mastered include website development, UI/UX design and data analysis. Dedicated to study hard and develop myself in the field of technology and information to benefit the surrounding.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### Remote Freelance, Mojokerto

Feb 2023 - Present

Jetis, Mojokerto

Web Developer

- Serve clients in creating specific websites according to their needs.
- Create a dynamic website UI/UX design using React.js and TailwindCSS technology.
- Develop the Back-end side of the website using Node.js technology and pay attention to system scalability.
- Implement REST API to integrate and simplify data exchange between the Back-end and Front-end sides of the Website.

### ATR/BPN Kantor Pertanahan kota Mojokerto

July 2022 - Dec 2022

Jl. Bhayangkara No.44, Mergelo, Prajurit Kulon, Kota Mojokerto

Internship

- Assist in the recapitulation and digitization of data in the KKP application of the Ministry of ATR/BPN in the Rights Determination and Registration Section.
- Analyze, Validate data and Geolocation of land boundaries from the Land Book with data in the KKP application of the Ministry of ATR / BPN.
- Recapitulate and print Electronic Mortgage and Roya deletion of Land Book Mortgage data on the Ministry of ATR/BPN CTF application and physical files.

#### **EDUCATION**

### Politeknik Elektronika Negeri Surabaya

Aug 2024 - Present

Distance Education - Associate Degree (D3)

Informatics Engineering

#### SMK Negeri 2 Mojokerto

July 2021 - May 2024

Software Engineering

#### **SMP Negeri 1 Jetis**

July 2018 - May 2021

Student

### LICENSE & CERTIFICATE

# **Learn to Create Front-End Web**

May 2024

Dicoding Indonesia - 10P8WW142XQK

#### Learn to Create Back-End Web

May 2024

Dicoding Indonesia - MEPJNNW8JX3V

**Learn Basic Web Programming** 

Dicoding Indonesia - NVP7Q7RYOZR0

**Learn Basic of Data Visualization** May 2024

May 2024

Dicoding Indonesia - 72ZDVV6V9ZYW

Learn Basic Structured Query Language (SQL)

May 2024

Dicoding Indonesia - 2VX3RREQ3ZYQ

Skill Competency Test Feb 2024

Penerbit : SMK Negeri 2 Mojokerto

Nomor : 400.3.8.1/431/101.6.27.5/2024

Predcatet : Very Competent

Course Using Laravel 8 Framework Oct 2023

MINARSIH TECH & SMK Negeri 2 Mojokerto

Internship Dec 2022

Penerbit: Kantor Pertanahan Kota Mojokerto

Nomor : 08/35.76/I/2023

### TECHNICAL SKILLS

• Web Development (Intermediate)

• Responsive Web Design (Basic)

• UI/UX Design (Intermediate)

• Graphic Design (Basic)

• API Development (Beginner)

• Microsoft Office (Intermediate)

# **SOFT SKILLS**

Teamworking

- Time Management
- Critical and Analytical Thinking
- Problem Solving